Well then, shall we get right to it?
（サソリ）さて…
（サソリ）もうやるか
（春野はるのサクラ）来る
Here it comes!
（サクラ）うっ
（チヨの掛け声）
（サクラ）ああっ…
死ね！
Die!
（チヨ）速い
He's fast!
To think that Hiruko's tail
fell to pieces...
ヒルコの尾が バラバラとは
You've got some pretty good moves,
Granny Chiyo.
やるな チヨバア
In that case, how about this?
なら これでどうだ
Oh no!
（チヨ）いかん！
（サソリ）そらあ！
Take this!
（サソリ）ババアが操ってんなら
らちが明かねえ
With the old lady manipulating things,
it's impossible to get anywhere.
（サクラ）あっ
In that case...
だったら…
（サクラ）あっ
（チヨ）いかん！
Oh, no! Sakura! Hold your breath!
サクラ 息を止めろ！
Is it poison?!
（サクラ）毒…
Sakura--!
サクラ！
（デイダラ）
そろそろやるか うん
I guess it's about time to start...
Hold it, damn you!
（うずまきナルト）
待てってばよ こらあ！
（デイダラ）おいらもついてる
How lucky of me...
to take on two Jinchuriki...
２匹も人柱力をやれるとは
（ナルト）うっ
Damn!
（ナルト）クソ！
（はたけカカシ）ナルト！
Naruto!
うっ… はあ
逃がすか！
I'm not about to let him get away!
うっ
くっ…
（カカシ）うっ はっ
カ… カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei!
（デイダラ）
さすがに コピー忍者相手には
Against a Copy Ninja,
I guess one Detonating Clay
is a little pathetic...
起爆粘土１つじゃ
お粗末だったな うん
かといって
起爆粘土も残りわずかだ
Having said that,
there's only a little Detonating Clay left.
I was intending to only lure out
the Jinchuriki, but...
人柱力じんちゅうりき１人を
おびき出すつもりだったが
こりゃ やっかいだな うん
This is troublesome...
この… 待ちやがれ！
You jerk...wait!
（カカシ）待て ナルト！
Wait, Naruto!
チッ
（カカシ）
サクラたちから 離れすぎたな
We've moved too far away
from Sakura and the others.
しかも これ以上離れると無線が…
If we move even further away,
the radio transmission will...
I won't be able to contact Guy's group...
ガイ班と連絡が取れなくなる
We better hurry...
急がないと
♪～
～♪
Chiyo's Secret Skills
You ain't seen nothing yet!
（マイト･ガイ）まだまだ
（ガイ）おりゃあ
そりゃあ
とっ… クソ…
Damn...
これでは切りがない
There'll be no end to it this way...
（日向ひゅうがネジ）ハア…
ハア！ タア！
回天かいてん！
Rotation!
クソ… どうすればいい
Damn...
What should I do?
（テンテン）はっ
（テンテン）自分と戦うなんて
一体どうすればいいの
Fighting against yourself...
What the heck should I do?
Leaf...Hurricane.
（ロック･リー）木こノ葉は旋風せんぷう
ハア ハア…
I'm really starting to get tired...
いいかげん… 疲れてきました
（サソリ）
小娘は この毒で確実に死ぬ
This poison will kill that girl for sure...
（サクラ）うっ…
（サクラ）大丈夫
なんとか吸い込まずにすんだ
I'm okay!
I managed not to inhale it...
サクラ
Sakura!
させるか
You think I'll let you do that!
フン！
（サソリ）フフッ
くっ うくっ…
こ… これは
Th-This is...!
It's a Kunai Knife with a rope attached.
ロープ付きクナイだ
かわすんじゃなく
はじき返すんだったな
You should have repelled it,
rather than dodge it, eh?
I can't hold my breath...
（サクラ）息が続かない
Sakura!
（チヨ）サクラ…
（サソリ）フッフフ…
どうあっても サクラを逃さぬ気か
So you're determined not
to let Sakura go, are you?
It's useless, Granny Chiyo.
ムダだ チヨバア
この毒はちょっと吸い込んだだけで
死に至る
The poison will kill you by inhaling it
even with the slightest dose.
（チヨ）サクラ
Sakura...
フッ 終わったな
Looks like it's over...
Naruto...
（サクラ）ナルト
（サクラ）ごめんナルト
I'm sorry, Naruto...
少し待たせることになっちゃうけど
It'll mean I'll keep you waiting a little,
今度は きっと…
but I promise
I won't be a burden next time...
足手まといには ならないから
I promised Naruto...
（サクラ）ナルトと約束したんだ
今度は 足手まといにならないって
that this time I wouldn't
be a burden...
誓ったんだ
I promised him that...this time...
今度は 私が２人を守るって
I would protect the two of them...
I...can't...in a place like this!
私は こんなところで…
The poisonous smoke
will stop in a minute...
（チヨ）もうすぐ毒煙は止まる
持ちこたえてくれ サクラ
Hang in there, Sakura!
フッ…
I didn't plant only one source
of poisonous smoke...
毒煙の仕込みは
１つだけじゃねえぜ
What?!
（チヨ）何！
サクラ 待っておれ！
Sakura! Hold on!
（サクラ）
私は こんなところで死ねない
I...can't die...
in a place like this!
ん？
何？
What!
（チヨ）サクラ！
Sakura!
サクラ しっかりせい
Sakura, hang in there... Sakura!
サクラ！
（サソリ）へ～え
Not bad...
やるじゃねえか
This is bad! She's not breathing!
こりゃ いかん
息をしとらん
Are you all right, Sakura?
ああ 大丈夫か？ サクラ
Y-Yes...
（サクラ）はい
（チヨ）こヤツ
She...
Did she use the blast waves
of a Paper Bomb
起爆札の爆風で
毒煙を吹き飛ばしたのか？
to blow off the poisonous smoke?
Along with herself in it,
escaping the trap in the process...
しかも ワナから抜けるため自分ごと
How reckless of her...!
なんという ムチャを
You...!
あんたは…
I will capture you!
あんたは 私が捕まえる！
うっ… 手足が吹っ飛ぼうが
Even if my arms and legs
were to be blown off...
Even if I were to swallow poison
and become immobile...
毒をくらって動けなくなろうが
I will capture you, no matter what!
必ず捕まえる！
No matter how much
you might resist...
どんなに抵抗されようと
No matter what tricks
you come up with...
どんな手を使われても
I will make you tell me everything
about Orochimaru!
私が絶対に大蛇丸おろちまるのことを
吐かせてやる
You hear me?!
いいか！
Even though I said
I'd take the Jinchuriki,
（デイダラ）
人柱力をやるとは言ったものの
the Copy Ninja is a nuisance.
やっぱ コピー忍者は邪魔だな
I have to somehow separate
him from the Jinchuriki.
なんとか人柱力から
ヤツを引き離さなきゃな うん
（カカシ）ん？
（ナルト）あっ
うっ カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei!
ハッ さっすが！
Awesome!
That guy is trying by
any means possible
（カカシ）ヤツはなんとかして
to separate me from Naruto...
俺から ナルトを
引き離そうとしてるな
I see... So he's trying to go
against Naruto one-on-one.
なるほどな
ナルトと差しで
やり合おうってわけだ
ちぇっ 作戦は失敗か
Damn! So my strategy failed, huh.
I guess my only choice is to
target the two of them together.
やっぱ ２人一緒のところを
狙うしかねえか
I only have
a little Detonating Clay left...
起爆粘土も 残り少ねえし
If I knew it was gonna come to this,
こうなるんなら さっきのアジトに
I should have prepared
some more Detonating Clay
もっと起爆粘土の予備を
用意しておくんだった うん
back at the base...
Well, I do have a trump card...
まあ 奥の手はとってあるがな
（サクラ）あっ… えっ
Huh?!
When a woman is talking,
a man should listen quietly.
女がしゃべってるときは
男は静かに聞いてやるもんじゃ
あっ…
Oh...those things...
ああ… それか
So you remember these, huh...
（チヨ）覚えておったか
Yeah, I guess...
ああ 一応はな
That's right...
（チヨ）そうじゃ
They're the first puppets
you ever made.
お前が作った最初の傀儡くぐつ
The father and...
父ちちと…
the mother.
母ははじゃ
Father and mother?
“父と母”
You mean, Sasori's...
じゃあ サソリの
So what do you plan to do
with those now, huh?
いまさら そんなので
何しようってんだ
Those are puppets I made.
I already know its tricks.
俺の作った傀儡だ
手の内はバレバレだぜ
This is stupid...
くだらねえ
I wonder about that...
果たしてそうかのう
A wire?
（サクラ）ワイヤー？
Sakura! Stand back!
サクラ 下がっておれ
Okay!
はい
ハッ！
あっ… すごい
Amazing...
This is getting messy.
（サソリ）
さすがに面倒になってきたな
さっさと これ使うか
I better hurry up and
use this thing...
あっ…
ん…
As I thought, that puppet...
やはり その傀儡
三代目の術を
uses the Third Kazekage's Jutsu!
久しぶりだろ
You haven't seen this in a while,
have you...?
This Jutsu is why the Third Kazekage
was praised as the most powerful.
この術で三代目風影かぜかげは
最強とうたわれたんだからな
２人とも ぐちゃぐちゃだぜ
I'm gonna turn you guys into mush.
What the heck is that?
一体 何？
あれは 砂隠すながくれで
最も恐れられた武器
砂鉄さてつじゃ
♪～
～♪
むか～し昔 ある里に
燃えるように赤い髪をした
玉のようにかわいい男の子が…
きびだんご持って
鬼退治に出かけんだな
何言ってんの
まさかり担いで出かける話でしょ
あっ そうだった
いやいや 両親と
仲よく暮らしておったのよ
で 亀とか助けんのか？
全然 違うわよ
え～い やめたやめた
なんの話をしてるのか
分からなくなってしまったわい
（ナルト･サクラ）え～！
続きは？
次回「父と母」
（カカシ）やあ みんな
きょうは
木ノ葉の師弟関係についてだ
まずは 木ノ葉の創始者
初代火影ほかげ様
その弟 二代目
火の意志を受け継いだ三代目
そして その三代目の教え子が
伝説の三忍こと
自来也じらいや様 綱手つなで様 大蛇丸だ
綱手様からは シズネが
大蛇丸からは みたらしアンコが
自来也様からは四代目が
それぞれ教えを受けた
で 四代目の教え子が この俺
はたけカカシ というわけだ
そして これが
俺のかわいい教え子たち
ナルト サスケ サクラだ
とはいっても
サクラは 綱手様に弟子入りし
ナルトも 自来也様に
いろいろ教わっている
サスケは 里を出たっきり
なんの音沙汰もなし
（カカシ）
ちょっと さみしいねえ
あっ そこの君
よかったら
俺が先生やってあげようか
サービスしとくよ